It will be fine. Hang in there.
‫سيكون الأمر على ما يرام. اصمد.‬
Shoot me.
‫أطلقي عليّ النار.‬
Kill him…
‫اقتليه…‬
I'll save you.
‫سأنقذك.‬
Will you shoot me like you did before?
‫هل ستطلقين عليّ النار كما فعلت من قبل؟‬
Yes.
‫نعم.‬
And that will be the end of this.
‫وسينتهي الأمر بذلك.‬
The end…
‫النهاية…‬
What is the end?
‫ما هي النهاية؟‬
Many, many times I have seen the end.
‫رأيت النهاية مرات عديدة.‬
This is the end!
‫هذه هي النهاية!‬
You will die, and so will I.
‫ستموت وأنا أيضًا.‬
You've seen it?
‫هل رأيت ما حدث؟‬
What have you seen?
‫ماذا رأيت؟‬
What is it you've seen?
‫ما الذي رأيته؟‬
You don't know.
‫أنت لا تعرف.‬
I will tell you…
‫سأخبرك…‬
the truly horrifying story.
‫بالقصة الحقيقية المرعبة.‬
I'm back.
‫عدت.‬
A truly horrifying story, you say?
‫أتقولين قصة حقيقية مرعبة؟‬
The stories of the things that I saw.
‫قصص ما شهدته.‬
The many stories…
‫القصص العديدة…‬
that I told you about.
‫التي أخبرتك عنها.‬
After I was dragged from our home at the Three Frogs,
‫بعدما جُررت من بيتنا‬ ‫في مبنى "الثلاثة ضفادع"،‬
the place I was taken to
‫المكان الذي أُخذت إليه‬
was a pitch-black room with no walls.
‫كان غرفة مظلمة تمامًا ومن غير جدران.‬
I couldn't tell up from down or right from left in that room,
‫عجزت عن تمييز اتجاهات تلك الغرفة،‬
and everything I touched felt strange.
‫وكلّ ما لمسته في الغرفة كان له ملمس غريب.‬
I could tell that someone was watching me.
‫تبيّنت أن ثمة من يلمسني.‬
The room was completely silent.
‫كان الصمت يعمّ الغرفة.‬
Except occasionally I could hear screams from somewhere else.
‫إلا أنني في بعض الأحيان كنت أسمع صرخات‬ ‫صادرة عن مكان آخر.‬
The meals appeared out of nowhere.
‫كانت الوجبات تظهر من العدم.‬
I counted the meals.
‫أحصيت عدد الوجبات.‬
Five. Six. Seven.
‫خمسة. ستة. سبعة.‬
Eleven. Twelve. Thirteen.
‫11. 12. 13.‬
Twenty-one. Twenty-three.
‫21. 23.‬
Then when I'd lost track of the number…
‫وعندما أخفقت في العد…‬
That man appeared.
‫ظهر ذلك الرجل.‬
Now, listen well.
‫اسمعني جيدًا.‬
People can become whatever they want to be.
‫بوسع الناس أن يصبحوا ما يريدونه.‬
Dear me.
‫عجبًا.‬
Is it all right for a little child like you to be wandering around here?
‫هل من المقبول لطفل مثلك‬ ‫أن يجوب أرجاء المكان هنا؟‬
You see, this is the child.
‫هذا هو الطفل المراد.‬
The child?
‫الطفل المراد؟‬
My, you're so cute.
‫ما ألطفك.‬
So this is the child.
‫هذا هو الطفل إذًا.‬
Magnificent! What a beautiful child.
‫مذهل! ما أجمله من طفل.‬
Look, this is the child.
‫انظر، هذا هو الطفل.‬
This is the child, eh?
‫هذا هو الطفل.‬
What fine results.
‫يا لها من نتائج مذهلة.‬
Yes, very good results.
‫أجل، نتائج مذهلة.‬
Is this the child?
‫هل هذا هو الطفل؟‬
This is the one…
‫هذا هو المراد…‬
Let us now raise…
‫لنرفع الآن…‬
I only remember fragments of the speech that was given.
‫أتذكّر فقط أجزاءً من الخطاب الذي أُلقي.‬
…for us, the chosen elite.
‫…النخبة المختارة.‬
To the future of the country!
‫نخب مستقبل البلاد!‬
Cheers!
‫نخبكم!‬
First, one person collapsed.
‫سقط شخص واحد في البداية.‬
Those around him gathered around.
‫اجتمع من حوله الباقون.‬
Then those who gathered around began collapsing on top of one another.
‫ثم بدأ المجتمعون في السقوط فوق بعضهم بعضًا.‬
There were moans, screams, and shouts.
‫كان هناك أنين وآهات وصرخات.‬
The room was overflowing with fear.
‫عمّ الخوف الغرفة.‬
Of the 42 lives that were taken that day,
‫من بين الـ42 حياة التي حُصدت في ذلك اليوم،‬
Franz Bonaparta was the only one who remained.
‫كان "فرانس بونابارتا" الوحيد الذي نجا.‬
I ran.
‫ركضت.‬
I ran to escape from there.
‫ركضت للهرب من هناك.‬
I ran without even noticing
‫هربت من دون أن ألاحظ‬
that the thorns on the rose bush in the garden had injured me.
‫أن أشواك شجيرة الورود‬ ‫في الحديقة قد جرحتني.‬
When I arrived at the Three Frogs, you welcomed me back.
‫عندما وصلت إلى مسكن "الثلاثة ضفادع"‬ ‫رحّبت بعودتي.‬
I told you.
‫أخبرتك.‬
For days and days…
‫لأيام وأيام…‬
I told you about everything I experienced.
‫أخبرتك عن كل ما مررت به.‬
You're wrong.
‫أنت مخطئ.‬
You're wrong!
‫أنت مخطئ!‬
Nina.
‫"نينا".‬
Can you hear me, Nina?
‫أيمكنك سماعي يا "نينا"؟‬
Calm down, Nina.
‫اهدئي يا "نينا".‬
It's me, Tenma.
‫هذا أنا، "تينما".‬
You know me, right? It's me.
‫أنت تعرفينني، أليس كذلك؟ هذا أنا.‬
That's right. That's the way. Calm down.
‫أحسنت، أجل هكذا. اهدئي.‬
There. That's a good girl.
‫هاك. أحسنت.‬
It's all right. It's all right now.
‫أنت بخير. أنت بخير الآن.‬
That's wrong!
‫غير صحيح!‬
That's all wrong!
‫هذا غير صحيح!‬
That wasn't me!
‫لم أكن أنا!‬
It wasn't me who said, "Welcome back!"
‫لست من قالت "عودًا حميدًا".‬
The one who said that was…
‫من قالت ذلك هي…‬
What… I said was…
‫ما قلته أنا كان…‬
I'm back.
‫عدت.‬
Welcome back.
‫عودًا حميدًا.‬
Johan is wrong.
‫"يوهان" مخطئ.‬
Johan only listened to what I told him.
‫سمع "يوهان" فقط ما قلته له.‬
The one who was taken away to the Red Rose Mansion…
‫من أُخذ إلى قصر "الوردة الحمراء"…‬
to the Red Rose Mansion was me!
‫من أُخذ إلى قصر "الوردة الحمراء" هو أنا!‬
The one who was dragged away down the stairs at the Three Frogs…
‫من جُرّ إلى أسفل الدرج‬ ‫في مسكن "الثلاثة ضفادع"…‬
The one who counted the meals in the pitch-black room without walls…
‫من أحصى الوجبات‬ ‫في الغرفة المظلمة التي بلا جدران…‬
The one who stood there in the room filled with corpses…
‫ومن وقف هناك في الغرفة المليئة بالجثث…‬
That was all…
‫كلّ ذلك…‬
That was all me!
‫أنا من شهدته!‬
I'm scared…
‫أنا خائفة…‬
THREE FROGS
‫"(الثلاثة ضفادع)"‬
I'm back.
‫عدت.‬
Welcome back.
‫عودًا حميدًا.‬
Tell me everything.
‫أخبريني بكل شيء.‬
Well…
‫في الواقع…‬
What happened was…
‫ما حدث كان…‬
I told him…
‫أخبرته…‬
For days and days…
‫لأيام وأيام…‬
That's enough.
‫هذا يكفي.‬
I told Johan what I'd been through.
‫أخبرت "يوهان" بما مررت به.‬
Johan took my experiences and…
‫أخذ "يوهان" تجاربي…‬
You don't have to talk.
‫لست مضطرة إلى التحدث.‬
Johan took my experiences
‫أخذ "يوهان" تجاربي‬
and made them his own.
‫وادّعى أنها تجاربه هو.‬
It's my fault that Johan--
‫غلطتي أن "يوهان"…‬
That's enough!
‫هذا يكفي!‬
Just now…
‫وعملت الآن…‬
I told Johan everything.
‫على إخبار "يوهان" بكل شيء.‬
When Johan listened to me, he seemed to be smiling.
‫عندما سمعني "يوهان" بدا أنه يبتسم.‬
But he also seemed to be crying.
‫لكن بدا أنه يبكي أيضًا.‬
I've never seen a human… look that way before.
‫لم أر إنسانًا بهذه الصفات من قبل.‬
I couldn't… shoot him.
‫عجزت عن إطلاق النار عليه.‬
But I'm sure he will destroy himself.
‫لكنني متأكدة من أنه سيدمّر نفسه.‬
Just like I will.
‫كما سأفعل.‬
Don't!
‫إياك أن تفعلي هذا!‬
Just like I will destroy myself!
‫كما سأدمّر نفسي!‬
Don't you dare!
‫إياك أن تجرئي على فعل ذلك!‬
Don't do it.
‫لا تفعلي هذا.‬
If you die…
‫إن مت…‬
If anything happens to you…
‫إن أصابك أي مكروه…‬
what would I do?
‫فماذا سأفعل؟‬
If you died, where would I go?
‫إن مت، فإلى أين سأذهب؟‬
Go on living.
‫ابقي على قيد الحياة.‬
I'm begging you.
‫أتوسل إليك.‬
Stay alive no matter what happens.
‫حافظي على حياتك مهما حدث.‬
Please! I'm begging you!
‫أرجوك! أتوسل إليك!‬
Yes? It's me.
‫نعم؟ هذا أنا.‬
Did you find the car near the villa?
‫هل وجدت السيارة بالقرب من الفيلا؟‬
I did. It was driven off the cliff.
‫وجدتها. سقطت من على جرف.‬
Edward is dead inside.
‫"إدوارد" ميت في الداخل.‬
I'm pretty sure I know who did it.
‫أعرف يقينًا من فعلها.‬
Most likely, Johan has…
‫على الأرجح أن "يوهان"‬
gone to kill Franz Bonaparta.
‫ذهب لقتل "فرانس بونابارتا".‬
His son is in Prague.
‫ابنه في "براغ".‬
I told Johan that.
‫أخبرت "يوهان" بذلك.‬
I don't know if that will end things…
‫لا أعرف إن كان ذلك سينهي الأمور…‬
or if his destruction will end at just that.
‫أم أن ما يحدثه من تدمير‬ ‫سيتوقف بانتهاء ذلك.‬
The sister's memories.
‫ذكريات الأخت.‬
Something missing from her memories.
‫ثمة ما هو مفقود من ذكرياتها.‬
Johan has one other memory in him. That other memory…
‫ثمة ذكرى أخرى لدى "يوهان". تلك الذكرى…‬
What exactly was the thing that we imagined we were creating…
‫ما كان بالضبط الشيء الذي تخيّلنا أننا نعدّه…‬
Franz…
‫"فرانس"…‬
Franz Bonaparta…
‫"فرانس بونابارتا"…‬
Live.
‫ابقي على قيد الحياة.‬
I'm sure…
‫أنا متأكد‬
there is a place for you.
‫من أن ثمة مكان لك.‬
There is a place for us.
‫ثمة مكان لنا.‬
I know there is, somewhere.
‫أعرف أن ثمة مكان لنا.‬
Hi. I'm really glad you came.
‫مرحبًا. يسعدني قدومك.‬
I'm usually the one coming to you.
‫أنا عادةً من آتي إليك.‬
Come on. Come inside.
‫تفضّل. تفضّل بالدخول.‬
I'd just made some tea.
‫أعددت القليل من الشاي.‬
I've always wanted you to have some of my best tea.
‫لطالما أردت‬ ‫أن تتناول أفضل أنواع الشاي لديّ.‬
How is it?
‫ما رأيك؟‬
Do you like it? It's my very own special herb tea.
‫هل أعجبك؟ إنه شاي خاص بي أنا.‬
Since you've come all the way here to visit me,
‫بما أنك تكبدت عناء السفر لزيارتي،‬
this must be something important.
‫فلا بد من أن الموضوع مهم.‬
Ask for anything you like. I can be ready in no time.
‫اطلب أي شيء تريده.‬ ‫يمكنني الاستعداد في أسرع وقت.‬
Who do you want me to kill this time?
‫من تريدني أن أقتل هذه المرة؟‬
What? Stop messing with me.
‫ماذا؟ كفّ عن العبث معي.‬
Come on, cut it out.
‫بحقك، كفّ عن ذلك.‬
I've woken…
‫لقد أفقت…‬
from the dream.
‫من الحلم.‬
You must be tired.
‫لا بد أنك متعب.‬
What about the plan?
‫ماذا عن الخطة؟‬
I've awoken.
‫لقد أفقت.‬
Hey, hold on here.
‫مهلًا لحظة.‬
Then why the heck did I collect all that money?
‫لم جمعت كلّ هذا المال إذًا؟‬
I've woken from the dream.
‫أفقت من الحلم.‬
Why the heck did I kill all those people?
‫لماذا قتلت كل هؤلاء الناس؟‬
I've seen many scenes at the end.
‫شهدت الكثير من مشاهد النهاية.‬
But now I can see a different scene.
‫لكن باستطاعتي الآن رؤية مشهد مختلف.‬
It is the scene of the real end.
‫إنه مشهد النهاية الحقيقية.‬
The memory that only I have.
‫الذكرى التي لديّ وحدي.‬
Where I truly should be.
‫حيث يجب أن أكون.‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
The place I should be.
‫المكان الذي يجب أن أكون فيه.‬
MR. LIPSKÝ BONAPARTA
‫"السيد (ليبسكي بونابارتا)"‬
Ruhenheim.
‫"روهينهايم".‬
There it is.
‫ها هو ذا.‬